Just like your god. I
want to drive past. Get
up close but I think of. Our infant boy
and
a snake I am I
a. Dremel I am wrong I thank him
for the end
the Iraq.
The AS.
The you.
The the.
Sadness and.
The and I.
The the.
I'm
I'm. I'm
.
Why God my
and I saw my
I'll ride
another dog
neuron
I had I
chosen one why why
why
why why why why why
why why why
why why. Why
why why
why the
lure
Mike. Moore.
High that river is right now on the wall
the mud the sand it's grand and I'll never
run across. One.
I am. I not sure you're right
about out and I was. Out
we were both were rich and something wrong
on the tracks and they wanted to get
around this like it was controlling
not endure it in or out among.
The poor the
the little girl I was the land of
the remain alive. Our Get rid of
it keep trying I
pointed
the way
the
remember.
The unarmed
the
band the
icing
the pain. I mean all right. I'll get out.
But they're coming back if you back down.
The other girl.
I don't remember.
Thank you. And when
pressed.
My point.
Why
why. All
Why.
And more.
Why why.
That. Is why there are I think
provided as my mike out. There and
although I know I will now I'm
leaving the morning now and I'm not.
Well my oh my God I'm not going to do
that through the merits out of mind. That
it's not. It's not quite the attitude we're
going to curate work I'm not putting
a I'm going to bed you don't want more than
that of course it doesn't pay much but
well at least it's stuck are you
driving by then the three OK now.
I'm not I got me going to God
Thank you Mary it takes more than
intellect to be
a musician with your soul and. Good
luck marrying not buying theater next time
you're in thank you but I'm never coming
back.
I don't know about that girl or how demeaning
they were for years and they see with
they don't want to bring girls to Surat an
action that she'd feel of the something
like homeless or. Never Know What
She thing you know is kept pretty
much to ourselves maybe in her place I do
the same thing just pick up lines again.
She so quiet right see who's you like
my God I guess that's what it takes to
survive I still say she's
behaving great or. If she's got
a bad one it'll go around
while other you know.
Nurse the
sniper not
my hand my
the the
one
where.
The
Iran
the I'm
glad
the poor
crowd the
I'll wrap
the
knife I am
guy
huh
Iran
the
.
Uh
thanks
for.
The
rock.
Cool volcano.
The. VICAR.
Murmured
the right.
The world.
I always.
Felt in the lead up I.
Have anything else lady. Could you tell me
what that big sucker you might have been
I always mean you know back
out there and that used to be
a pretty rig late in the old
days and the lake went down in
a minute they're all out of work and they
brought those buildings up there made
some starlet carnival after
a while. That years ago though
this pans out there now at.
Apple Apple your apple running How could
you know. Oh here that it's right over
here
a little later. Bank
back after I left Iran yes.
By that what I am Indian now and then
a regular room and now now I
only got you the land now how.
Are you. Even when I watch you won that
one out. Things right now
be quite comfortable when.
I'm down there I have my back on her now
the young can even I'm not what I want.
Right goodnight I'm. I am.
Why why why
why why.
Why why why. I
wired.
And they dismissed ten rings in our eyes
and. You know the maiden thank them
wrapping them in no coats that's where we
heard about you oh by the way you have
like yep I had
a good. Day We hope you're going to like
it here we're not allowed to strip in this
area of course but we haven't lived
congregation we that have ordered resection
they want the beach could we go get them
if. I don't go to prison that's Luke maybe
this is a I don't know what some
of the ladies were. They say on
a priority that should be
enough. Course we'll know
that for the time being but my
dear you cannot live in isolation
from the human race to mine
I got my I want you to.
Why why why why why when
I had my heart when
the or when or when where
or when.
You're.
More
like my horror when I when I
when I Why
why why why or why when I
when I heard
or when I
wore
while I was the
wrong man why.
I. Pour why
why my
During the
American I
for one.
Practical got me you need
a break here I gotta make
a call out at the lake would you
like come along for the run.
All right but look out
of your life I work on.
The you're.
That used to be quite right it's been too
good to long run now when you take me
good news no it isn't they pout any more
at why they put up this barrier he got
anything to step around with. What
a crack in could be when you think
I'm not I really and I don't.
Have my back nothing more I don't have
a clue. What you talk Marko.
A lot like the limit when we
got a mic or
a minister to break the law wouldn't.
Maybe I can come back come out of my
alley alone now.
My.
Eyes are bad I'm going to need
a good. I read about the
fireman guy walk out that I
went Well I'm grabbing the
kind of man you want.
At Marquette. And I got out of.
It and grabbed. At. What hour that
I better grab it and have
it made now back. On
the bench that many here why I want
to make up the bed in the back.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
The of.
Iraq. Yeah yeah kind of but.
I'm Jonathan I'm unique right now I think
it may be either I want to I'm going to
run for.
The thank you.
I'm cutting to get my manhunt I
guess I am or I am. Pumped up in
a way whether we I could thought we would
be unable to follow it I'm ignorant and
you that I realized. Very
quickly but I got in on
a matter I'm getting at by the
Iraq you. Might recognize.
A guy that. I'm going to rank my room. For
him on. Her.
And that.
We want to. Thank you.
Thank you for. The you.
I am can.
Thank you.
Thank
. YOU THANK YOU. And
then I'll let out my. Talk
I want. To commend all.
All. Right Mina Till then we had the room.
I mean the other one. You
know there is. Me and you in
metal then there. Are
a girl or is that out because you
might have been up in your gig in.
That. Damn thing and I am I Maybe
you're in the border. Then you
know how the Street works
in Miami here and I.
Now know how badly I have gotten there.
You know oh there they are they're big
enough to the to the high demand even.
You get got to not let your
imagination run away with the thing.
And no but I. Mean to
go any better than we
can. Now we're going to cause
a big if you weigh. You
see.
The black.
Out good mommy I know I
don't. Like I can I.
But I got
a day off right I make it my world they
have to lock it up. I get ready to come
over here I. Got my what
I need to the cause.
I get you to wrong my me on
these are and I thought well.
I'm glad I didn't and do not
know what I can buy I don't know
a big word the ordinary guy work no way
out that's all but it might be the guy
but I got
a couple shots up the last much longer ya
know ain't it now the recommended bank
like your children Oh is
that what you do I mean
a hey come out of the play the organ
in church church. Hey I don't mind
about that I just didn't know you're a
church were to me entered to death like
a big. Who has a funny way to look at.
People seem shocked because I took
a job in
a church and I I regarded simply the time
I mean there's no organised mapmaker in
it. Thinking like that to
give you nightmares by
the man. That we met with
that painted feeling that.
I can
a lot and I. Probably. Mean I.
Thank God and. Then I think back and I can
bet that no one I owe.
Make the mortgage and.
I had to get the church organ and
I thought that even college I got
a college. Football but
they want to me to take
a lot of classes and think you know they're
that way. Out of the next guy and I
didn't think they would teach in
school you know and they hired
a Moses principal product.
You know you know like
a principal product to Brazil.
Coffee being the snake Oh I feel like that.
I was good I couldn't care less how you
and I care about a girl in the
article I. Don't know what
a graduated. But imagine you. Come
I would be an alcoholic I just
like to start the day open
a good mood so you might
be led by a new. Kind of
a guy employing one you know the happy
worker. That make your one happy.
Morning I that me right. And
then even the I don't know J.
. I hope I follow the play of the law
and thank you Bob. Thank you
I've got the letter but. I
want to turn killer died but I am.
In and took up the wrong impression of me
I'm going to get I mean I think I have.
Like I said. I can imagine
it but I. Wouldn't you
know I had the same
a shopping. Because
I had
a nice back when I think the right. To
drive the price otherwise there and
I'm I'm sure it isn't
that I think it makes
a second Trek but I think we have the
neck right out of Iran that you write
about here getting them.
Her.
Work.
Why.
What is it that my. I didn't mean
any harm I just got to get it great
now. What was that my when.
I said I was the one out
there I had with the guy but
now look look you had
a fight if there were you won't solve
anything about control yourself I'm Dr sent
my office is right across
the street you got
a shot you would like my is that the
public not to offer it. Could I come
again after certain I'll take over
my off with the the tubes All right.
I'm back with anyone it was
a. Fight and I know
I had no play. No part of the law were me
and then you saw this man.
You'll excuse my back but I want to get
some of that written down I'm not talking
for an hour Anything else
anything you haven't told me.
That's the whole story and found that now
that he's doing this that's simple but
was it what do you mean you could not have
been in the park the seven zero one of
us men would have seen him and that
night in the hallway you send yourself
a man and he came up
a minute later and she didn't see in the
jeep were you driving that and less than
a week since you were in
a car that crashed into the river how you
got out of that no one seems to know but
that experience must have been
a serious emotional shock I think I imagine
got out of it don't you think I mean I
didn't say that I don't mean that
I'm a competent or anything I'm
a realist I'm not get into imagining
any hogwash all of us imagine things
I've never heard two men talking behind
your back and imagine they were talking
about you that you never imagined you saw
someone you knew and walked up to them
and they were explained your I can see
what that has to do I think the point is
that our imaginations Patricks honest they
often misinterpret what we see and hear
you agree. In fact can
happen in ordinary times go
a step further look what can happen in
a high fever following us or is emotional
shock. About that I could have imagined
all of this this man this thing
resembling And when you've got
a known and acquaintance or your
father know your wife's been here
a back row now how did Guy one never know
right and I sat saying. I think so
and I have no desire within the
company about this Have you always
thought this right. I don't know
don't you want to join in the things that
other people do share the experiences of
other people I don't think they were being
that close. I'm sure the crap that I'm
trying to make out brother got
a thing do you feel guilty wanting
them. I don't I'm bad I'm not
a psychiatrist and perhaps I'm being clumsy
and all that but I am suggesting that
perhaps there's
a good represent the guilt feeling I have
that they can and they've been frankly I
don't know I know what. My magination are
going to put. You know very strong well
that's not true I go by backwards you mean
that or probably end up at the light somehow
you associate it with all that don't
you go out. The butt and then go back to
a car and I don't base think it is about
my mouth to make sure I could but if Dr
maybe but at least someone to be with you
now I can I get the I'm back going to
where we're primed to go out
there are more. Apt I can go all
out.
What
your war one
war
now.
You for
a. War
.
Why.
They ask. I don't want to get turned down
again I was thinking that you know that
I found out about you know the way anyway
I had to pack up the test that was good.
About it I got over the blade
that I don't buy I know my
identity I. Say Yeah do you mind if I had
you what I wanted and then I never put
you right and then you have paid and
then. This is the cold. What I'm about to
call the remedy this morning I
need the company. Making me
company tonight but in
what way home oh yeah.
I should be in
a thread I'm going with that I
had the baby by. The day after.
Day in church. Or were her
or
week the
was or with.
The OWS to you with.
Our.
Or with.
Our
when I or low. And I. And
I.
Would.
Put the auto or world.
War. The OR or the use of
the little war
during.
Our war.
The guy.
Was. All plain Starkweather
But are you playing
a master because you know Reese
and real people know what I want.
And I feel sorry for you and your
lack of how the art of the music up
distract the things have meaning and
significance to us I assume they did to you
but without this awareness. I'm
afraid you cannot be our organ
incontinence I must ask you to resign.
Not me I'm abandoning nor should you turn
your back on the church here on Earth
like that.
Either I've been waiting
a long time for you Mike I'm just over
there I don't trust the right place to go
the can the can
the stand.
The pain.
Tomorrow to drink either not really I really
out of there if you don't drink really
ask me that. Hour maybe I
not only bring reality I am
really dreck.
If you like the music I like you
don't like it you don't like to and
I drink the life from I hold you close
that. I couldn't say that you have said
anything the evening I don't play
that song again you like it so
much.
A Johnny was
a dom. But you know it you come on I've
been holding out on me that's not the kind
of pick you usually drag around you could
look at your job see that you're glad you
want to bet. Lay off one. Of them and
listen I'll help you put it over I
don't want you to think I know. Good
luck. When you know.
Yet. College.
Boy about this girl who want me. To be
a maid. Said how could I
don't like that you know.
That you were in the scene to join my
company that's not you know. I may
be yapping. My Jimmy but not if.
I get my head join
a party trying to. Pay
good money for that stuff in
a voice. I had no idea
oh. No I don't give you
what you said let's take
a class. And you got to me just home by.
Now with everything I say in the OK
You know I'm out. Mike
I want to be with you.
Just with anybody with you know the it.
I'm feeling all out there.
Are many want to be
I'll be the No come on. I'm not
being with you really I do.
I don't want to be
a long night. I want to be here you. Mean
that. Yes.
I. Want to you make it out of
him. You know my role only
a couple of the old. Is likely
to get very hot on the idea.
That.
The you know I it's. The bad I want to get
another.
Ad money. I want to go in there like.
I've. Been you know I
have to be alone and I.
Think I'm in why I'm here.
I think it won't be
a laundry in. The
next year ask me yet. Like
a little one. And
.
I'll the crap Thank you.
And with Matthew what's
going on around you
how was I when you. Carry back to me
the I'm getting the the. Mesa I just
want me get me out how
world Balrog the crap
I'll. Crash crash crash while
been the
prayer while I was when I
read the
world
yes.
But you cannot we're not very
much I'm afraid I'm sure glad
you have happened there are I'm gonna
come right down right after I think
I came on her I don't think your boss there
ever since she left my office yesterday
what's she going to do with the
devil remember what. I heard her
going on around that room all night never
heard that's going on and she wouldn't
let me in a room this morning she's
a strange one. She absolutely refuses my
help I can see that I blame or there's
something about her that completely baffles
me I urged her to call on me she feels
she needs help and I hope
she will. I tag last I am
a coward want to worry about she's determined
to leave the city and she wants to
get away as soon as
possible I hope she does.
I hope she can.
Keep.
The gap the girl at.
The Greek I know you're
whispered Radwin to the rabbi.
I was. Exile
Rigney
bought my
mom when my
the world arrive the
world in
the bank
alright. And
Rabbi grabs the new paragraph. And.
All
right
of the rat. In the car while
Trevor what did I get out of.
The IF. It's the.
My
aunt while I was my
why why why
my
I am
a man my name my. The
actor out for
what.
The course. The
doorway
of
the
of.
The
the wall.
And it's an X.
Box Live I look at on. The
at the.
The I want to get out of the.
I want to get away from.
All. The old the in
a nightmare.
The
but. You.
The cash.
The
you.
Thank the rat
the
rat
.
The poor girl.
When you're the Negro.
At the bank.
You.
The you.
All right.
All right
we're going to work with
it any. Think EPPER
and remember can.
There be we're not going to go. And
are looking for and trying
to prevent me from living.
The get me back the way I can't I
don't I don't know what really
anymore. Part of my
my life. If you don't know
what I said you go back
to trying to keep the word.
In God to tell me what you can do
I.
The name of the game is.
The and.
The AM.
The the.
The
I'm.
point
the
don't.
Ah.
You.
Or
women lol lol lol the poor.
Mary
Matalin the
OS.
Mary
am all
all the
. You.
I rather
morrow
wrapped
around Iraq war or when
you
. Were.
Our. Our
our our.
Our our. World our
nightmare in
a I'd rather.
It cry still over there and then
up what then Canadian up they had.
Them up.
Hour.
Why
why. The
why why
why.
I wore. My well I
had.
I had.